mangable.com 2011-05-20

# Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

At Mangable.com, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use visit Mangable.com, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties.

## Log Files

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site. 

## E-mail Communications

Mangable is very concerned about your privacy and we will never provide your email address to a third party without your explicit permission. Mangable may send out e-mails with Mangable-related news and updates. You may also receive notification e-mails from Mangable, which inform you of actions (e.g. New Account Registration) that have been performed on the site. Additionally, you may receive emails of updates in series information, all of which can be managed through your user dashboard once logged in. If you do not want to receive e-mail from us, please reply to the email. Additionally, to manually unsubscribe from the emails, set all anime to 'dropped' via your dashboard. However, please note that in all cases you will continue to receive all system e-mails (e.g. those regarding forgotten user passwords) and legal notices (e.g. updates to our policies) from us. 

## Cookies and Web Beacons

We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums.

## 3rd Party Advertisers

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/).  
You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.
